# DENISE AGUIRRE

#### S O F T W A R E D E V E L O P E R



- +54 9 11 2658-0740
- deniseaguirre.m@gmail.com
- San Miguel, Bs As, Argentina
- https://denise-aguirre-m.netlify.app/

## **PROFILE**

I am a software developer with experience in the MERN Stack, training in Electronic Commerce and Full Stack Web Development. I always look for opportunities to learn and create innovative technology solutions with a strong emphasis on user experience.

## SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- · Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Back End Coding
- Tester QA Manual

## EXPERIENCE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Bigger

2023 - 2024

 Software Developer in two projects, using the following technologies: NestJS, NextJS, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, TypeORM, Typescript, TailwindCSS, Cypress, Jest. SCRUM methodology, ClickUp, Slack

#### MERN FULL STACK DEVELOPER

**Bootcamp MindHub** 

2023 - 2023

- Metodology "learning by doing"
- Create and design responsive web applications from start to finish using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, MERN (MongoDB, Express, React and Node.js).
- Create mobile applications
- Learn to use third-party libraries in your projects such as Vue.js, Jquery, Bootstrap, Axios, among others.
- Learn to effectively analyze the projects you worked on and defend the decisions made.
- Use and integrate third-party APIs in an application.

## EDUCATION

#### MERN FULL STACK DEVELOPER

MindHub

2023 - 2023

# UNIVERSITY TECHNICIAN IN ELECTRONIC COMMERCE

National University of José C. Paz

2017 - 2020

# BACHELOR ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT OF ORGANIZATIONS.

Instituto Cristo Rey 2007 - 2009

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- HTML
- CSS
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Axios
- GitHub
- Redux
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- Nest
- Node
- Express
- PostgreSQL
- Cypress
- Jest

- Create, complete and secure web applications following the most used frameworks.
- Learn to segment problems, address them, read documentation and stay up to date on new technologies.
- Write clean, modular and efficient code, following good practice standards.

# TECHNICAL ASSISTANT OF THE VIRTUAL MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT

National University of José C. Paz

2019 - 2023

- Moodle database administration and virtual classroom design with HTML and CSS.
- Online classroom and student management.
- Preparation of frequently asked questions and tutorials.

#### DIGITAL MARKETING ASSISTANT

GardenLife S.A

2018 - 2018

- Customer service and online sales.
- Tracking orders and claims.
- Uploading and modification of products on the company's website and Mercado Libre. Creation of specifications and description of products published on the web.
- Management of Social Networks.

